《行尸走肉》前情提要
Previously on AMC's The Walking Dead…
这是哪儿
What is this place?
这是可持续生活的开始
This is the start of sustainability, community.
瑞克 他的团队非常危险
Rick, his group… they're dangerous.
诺亚因你而死
Noah died because of you.
你还想杀了我
You tried to kill me.
为什么
Why?
因为所有生命都很宝贵
Cause all life is precious.
开枪
Do it.
瑞克
Rick?
这听起来确实不实际
I know this sounds insane,
但这本来就是一个疯狂的世界
but this is an insane world.
在他们过来之前 我们要主动出击
We have to come for them before they come for us.
就这么简单
It's that simple.
明早我们就开始行动
This is where it all starts tomorrow.
托宾开这辆卡车
Tobin gets in the truck,
打开出口 我们就在后面就位
opens the exit and we're off.
然后跳下车 和大部队在
He hops out, catches up with his team at red.
路的西面 红气球那儿会合
staying on the west side of the road.
达里尔骑他的摩托
Daryl gets on his bike…
你看那儿
You see that?
挡不住了 我们得马上开始行动
It's open! We got to do this now!
现在就行动
We're doing this now!
托宾的小队 开始了 快
Tobin's group, get moving, go!
不行 瑞克 我们还没准备好
No, Rick, we're not ready.
萨莎 艾伯拉罕
Sasha! Abraham!
没错 我们现在就开始了
Damn straight, we'll do it live.
你和达里尔在红气球那碰头
You meet Daryl at red.
让他引着行尸去通道那儿
Let him take them through the gauntlet.
- 好 我们到时候见 - 走
- Yeah, we meet at red. - Go!
瑞克 我在「车队」那儿会发信号
Rick, I'll hit the tractor place.
好 还有谁
Okay, who else?
我们得把他们引开 否则数量太多了
We got to take them out or they'll distract the horde.
- 我来 让我帮你 - 不用
- I'm here, let me help. - No.
- 我来 - 那你得照我说的做
- I'm here! - Do everything I say.
- 我会的 - 瑞克 我们得演练一次
- I will. - Rick, this was supposed to be a dry run.
- 达里尔 准备好 - 他们来了
- Daryl, get ready. - They're coming.
瑞克 我们没有详细讨论过整个计划
Rick, we haven't even gone through the whole plan.
你要是想走就走 反正我们已经开始了
You want to go back, go back. We're finishing this.
托宾 等我的指令开车
Tobin, you hit it on my signal.
他们朝这边来了 我们别无选择
They're heading for home. We don't have a choice.
准备发射照明弹
Get ready to hit the flares.
现在
Now!
托宾 发动卡车
Tobin, hit the truck!
《行尸走肉》
你错了
You were wrong.
罗恩
Ron.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
Of course.
好了
Okay.
格伦
Glenn.
格伦 怎么了 你还好吗
Glenn, what happened? Are you okay?
我没事
I'm okay.
你们看起来很糟糕啊
You guys look like shit.
她没事了
She's fine. She's fine. She's okay.
塔拉
Tara?
我没事
I'm okay.
你看看他们吧
You just check on them.
- 我没事 - 怎么了
- I'm okay. - What happened?
我们出去了一趟
We were out there.
碰到了行尸… 我们都没事
The walkers and… we're all right.
被乱飞的子弹误伤的
Got winged by a ricochet.
没事的
It's all right.
我的天
Holy shit.
真好
Thank god…
你的发型没乱
Nothing happened to your hair.
好吧 尤金吓到我了
Okay, Eugene's freaking me out.
有谁能让诺亚来保护我一下吗
Somebody want to send Noah in here to protect me?
（对不起 我很混蛋 来华盛顿 新世界需要 瑞克·格兰姆斯）
你是对的
You were right.
还没结束
It wasn't over.
我们明天再详谈吧
We should talk more tomorrow.
听着
Listen…
我不想再冒险了
I don't take chances anymore.
那就别冒险
And you shouldn't.
你们各自都分配了任务
You all have your assignments.
知道在哪儿集合
You know where to rendezvous.
达里尔引那些行尸过去
Daryl leads them out.
萨莎和艾伯拉罕跟他们在山底会合
Sasha and Abraham join him at the bottom of the hill.
格伦 当你引行尸到「车队」那儿时
Glenn, you hit us.
给我们发信号
when you take care of the walkers at the tractor place.
那是我们成败的关键
That's the one thing we gotta get ahead of.
大家记得保持冷静
Everybody keep your heads.
保持清醒
Just keep up.
他在里面没问题吗
So, is he okay with it?
本来就是他想出来的
It was pretty much his idea.
他能理解
He gets it.
该洗个澡睡觉了
It's got a bed and a bath,
不过还是和监狱一样
but it's still a cage, you know?
他能理解
He gets it.
他告诉了我那辆卡车到底怎么回事
He told me what happened out there with the trucks.
他遇见那些人的事也和你说了
He tell you about those guys he met?
那些头上有「W」的人
The W's.
和我们看见的行尸头上一样
Like that walker we saw, yeah.
我们需要更多监测点
We need more watch points.
我会告诉狄安娜 不要再接纳任何人了
And I'm gonna tell Deanna we don't need to go looking for people anymore.
你不同意吗
You feel different about it?
是啊
Yeah, I do.
外面的人
Well, people out there,
他们会照顾好自己
they got to take care of themselves,
和我们一样
just like us.
我要把他放出去
I'm gonna get him out.
不该让他留在这里太久
Shouldn't leave him in there any longer than we have to.
你还好吗
You good?
嗯
Yeah.
我在努力
I'm trying.
听着 如果你还在乱想些什么…
Listen, if you're still looking to go buck wild with the breath impaired…
你已经问过这个问题 我也回答过了
You already asked the question and I already answered it.
如果你这么担心 干嘛还要和我一起上车
If you were so worried, why the hell did you get into the car with me?
听着 干这种惊心动魄的事
Listen, doing something as big as this…
才叫生存
That's living.
到了
There it is.
我们到了山脚下红气球的位置
We're at red at the bottom of the hill.
好的 行尸部队来了
All right, here comes the parade.
你这棍术从哪儿学的
Where'd you learn that?
一个朋友
A friend.
灾变之前还是之后
Before or after?
我问你答
I ask, you answer.
基本的礼貌 对吧
It's common courtesy, right?
之后
It was after.
一切发生后
After everything.
我很抱歉 但不得不问
Look, I'm sorry for this, for having to do this.
没关系
It's all right.
在我看来
The way I look at it,
当你走投无路时 更安全
sometimes you're safer when there's no way out.
我们得重新了解对方了
Got to get to know each other again.
第一次
For the first time…
重新认识
Again.
是我们
Hey, it's us.
我们回来了 让我们进去吧
We're back. You gonna let us in or what?
这么做是不允许的 所以我不会开门
I'm technically not authorized, so I will not be doing so.
- 你是谁啊 - 你先说
- Who the hell are you? - You first.
我叫希恩
I'm Heath.
我住在这儿 我的小队前几周出去执行任务了
I live here. My team's been on a run the last couple weeks.
我叫尤金
I'm Eugene.
亚伦接纳了我和我的团队
Aaron brought myself and my group here directly within that window,
所以我们之前从没见过 我也不确定你的身份
so we haven't had the chance to meet and I can't exactly confirm your residence.
开门
Open the gate.
如果我开了 要怎么确认你不是想杀了我
If I do, how do I know you won't attempt to kill me?
听着 我不会杀你
Okay, look, I'm not gonna kill you.
但你让我等得越久
But the longer you make me wait,
我越想狠狠揍你一顿
the more you motivate me to beat your ass, so…
谢谢
Thank you.
狄安娜让你来看门了
So Deanna put you on gate duty?
不 我只是暂时顶替霍利的班
Oh, no, I'm not proper duty. This is Holly's shift.
我刚好经过
I was just walking by.
她问我能不能顶替她一下
She asked if I could relieve her for a few ticks.
我说「不行 谢谢」 但她完全无视我
I said, "no, thank you" and she ignored me,
结果我在这等了她好久
which is obviously what I should have done.
她都没有回来
as it's been at least five ticks and still no Holly.
我叫斯科特 她叫安妮
I'm Scott. This is Annie.
你好
Hi. Good to meet you.
你们团队有多少人
How many of you are there?
十三个
13.
我是说 十二个人
I mean, 12.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我来关门
I'll close up.
我们不在的时候发生了什么大事吗
Anything big happen while we were gone?
昨晚我们开了个会
Well, we had a meeting last night.
噢 讨论了什么
Oh, yeah? About what?
你还是去问狄安娜吧
You might want to talk to Deanna.
让她亲自和你说
Get it from the horse. Her mouth.
明吧什么意思吧
You know?
明白
Right.
嘿 很高兴遇到和我一样的人
Hey, it's good to see someone like me.
我很喜欢你的发型
I fully respect the hair game.
- 谁建的围墙 - 他们
- Who put up the wall? - They did.
是个叫雷格的人
There was a man, Reg.
他做的计划 一直持续了下去
He drew up plans, made it happen early on.
这里有好多人
A lot of people in here.
一开始就在这里
They've been inside from the start.
有食物 有能源 行尸也不多
They had food, energy, not a whole lot of walkers.
就这么生活着
They just lived.
不需要拼了命活下去
They haven't had to survive.
他们认清我们之后 接纳了我们
They figured that out, brought us in.
看来还是太迟了
Still might be too late.
什么太迟了
Too late how?
他们太后知后觉了
For them to come around.
再说吧
We'll see.
你要去和狄安娜聊聊
You'll have to talk to Deanna.
她是这里管事的
She's the woman in charge.
之前是雷格的老婆
She was married to Reg.
之前
Was?
你们在做什么
What are you doing?
我们…
We're…
我想帮忙
I wanted to help.
一个人就够了
We only need one.
这里有两具尸体
We have two men here.
杀手不能埋在社区里面
We're not gonna bury killers inside these walls.
我明白你的感受
I understand how you feel.
真的
I do.
但这你做不了主
But it's not your decision.
托宾
Tobin.
瑞克说得对
Rick's right.
把尸体搬走
Take it away.
去西边
Go west.
沿着布兰顿路开几英里
Down Branton Road a few miles.
过了桥就停下来
Just past the bridge.
再远我们也去不了
We don't go out that way.
就把他扔树下
Let the trees have him.
我开枪打死他 因为他杀了雷格
I shot him because he killed Reg.
就这个原因 我们没得选
That was it. We didn't have a choice.
你们有牢房
You do have a cell.
那不是为杀手准备的
Not for killers.
我也是杀手 瑞克
I'm a killer, Rick.
我是杀手 你也是
I am, and you are, too.
格伦 你们到了吗
Glenn, you there yet?
快了 我们到之前能搞定
Almost. We'll have it handled before they get here.
我们在黄色气球这里见
And we'll meet you at yellow.
收到
Copy that.
能挡住的
It'll hold.
那就好
Well, that's good.
想想我们站的地方有多危险
You know, considering where we're standing.
米琼恩
Michonne.
嗯
Yeah?
之前你在那里
Back when you were in that place…
就是我住的地方
Where I lived…
是不是拿了我一根蛋白棒
Did you take one of my protein bars?
没有
No.
知道吗 我发誓那里还剩一罐花生酱
See, I could have sworn there was one more peanut butter left.
事情就是这样的 对吗
That's how it is, isn't it?
你总是觉得还剩一罐花生酱
You always think there's one more peanut butter left.
摩根
Morgan.
我们就把他扔这里吧
Maybe we just leave him here.
你不是这样的人
That's not who you are.
我知道的
I know.
嘿
Hey.
你不用这样
You don't.
摩根
Morgan.
停下
Stop.
你听到了吗
Did you hear that?
你来这做什么 罗恩
What are you doing out here, Ron?
我想知道我爸被埋在哪里了
I wanted to know where my dad was buried.
原来是这样的
This is how.
是怎样
How what?
社区是如何一直保存的
How the community's still here.
他们让部分行尸留在围墙边
They've had walkers at their walls,
但是更多的行尸 可以说大量的行尸
but a lot of them, maybe most of them,
都困在这里
they wound up here.
罗恩
Ron.
- 罗恩 - 我要回去了
- Ron. - I'm going back.
- 嘿 - 我没事
- Hey. - I'm fine.
你不该来这里
You shouldn't be out here.
我才不管你怎么想
I don't care what you think.
这不是我怎么想的 是我知道什么
It's not what I think, it's what I know.
你保护不了你自己 我会教你
You can't protect yourself. I'll show you how,
但是现在你不知道自己在做什么
but right now you have no idea what you're doing.
你要是离开 必死无疑
And if you come out here, you're gonna die.
死得绝不痛快 而且不会就这么死去
And it won't be quick and it won't ever be over.
因为你会变成它们
'cause you'll be one of them.
这就是会发生的事情
That's what's gonna happen.
现在你要和我们一起回去
You're coming back with us now.
别让我难做
Don't make it hard.
格伦 你得快点了
Glenn, you have to hurry.
声音会把尸群从路上吸引开
The noise could distract the herd right off the road.
- 快回话 - 我们到了
- Talk to me. - We're here.
看来数量不少
Sounds like a lot.
- 得让它们安静 - 你打算怎么做
- We need it quiet. - So what's the plan?
把它们放出来 每次就放几个
Take 'em out a few at a time.
尼古拉斯 你去门那里
Nicholas, you're at the door.
好了
All right.
就放一两个出来 然后关门
You let one or two out and then you close it.
一直这么做 这就是计划 这样来控制它们
You keep doing that. That's the trick. That's how we control it.
希恩
Heath…
等一下 万一门他关不上怎么办
Wait, what if he can't close it?
- 我可以的 - 那我们就带上它们
- I'll be able to. - Then we take them on.
带上它们
We take them on?
要是有麻烦了 我们就跑去房子后面
If we get into trouble, we go behind the building.
进入林子 把他们一起引过去
into the woods and we draw them away.
嘿 他来的时候你还在外面执行任务
Hey, you've been out on runs since he got here.
他清楚自己在做什么
He knows what he's doing.
我和艾登完全不知道
Me and Aiden, we didn't.
应该先彩排一下的
This was supposed to be a dress rehearsal.
我本来应该在送披萨的 兄弟
I'm supposed to be delivering pizzas, man.
达里尔在把它们带过来
Daryl's leading them this way.
很快就要到了
and they're closing in.
声音会把尸群从路上吸引开
That noise is gonna pull the herd right off the road.
那时候我们问题就大了
and then we have serious trouble.
没别的办法了
We have to do this.
好吧
Yeah, okay.
- 好了吗 - 好了
- Okay? - Okay.
- 好 - 好的
- Okay. - Okay.
准备好
All right.
我数到三 准备好了吗
On three. Ready?
一
One…
二
Two…
三
Three!
该死
Shit!
我的队伍
My team…
我们早些时候
We saw it early on,
去做第一班侦查的时候
back when we were on one of those first scouts,
弄清楚了周围的情况
finding out what was around here.
山脚下有一个营地
There was a camp at the bottom.
事态恶化的时候 那些人肯定
The people, they must have.
用一辆卡车
blocked the exits with one of those trucks.
堵住了缺口
back when everything started to go bad.
他们没成功 都成了行尸
They didn't make it. They were all roamers.
大概有十几个
Maybe a dozen of them.
之后一个都没回来吗
No one's been back since?
华盛顿
D.C.
所有值得搜刮的城镇都在另一个方向
Every town worth scavenging are all in the other direction.
我绝对不想
And I never really felt like.
在那个变成行尸的营地边上野餐
having a picnic next to the camp that ate itself.
一直都是声音在吸引行尸
So all the while the walkers have been drawn by the sound.
这些行尸弄出更多声音 吸引了更多的行尸
and they're making more sound and they're drawing more in.
事情就是这样
And here we are.
我知道我的计划
Now what I'm proposing,
听起来很冒险
I know it sounds risky,
但是行尸已经要从出口处溜过来了
but walkers are already slipping through the exits.
那个行尸可以钻过来的卡车
One of the trucks keeping the walkers in.
早晚有一天会抵挡不住
could go off the edge any day now.
也许就是一场大雨的事
Maybe after one more hard rain.
那个出口朝东
That exit sends them east.
所有僵尸都会向东而来 正对我们
All of them. Right at us.
问题不是那辆卡车是否挡得住
This isn't about if it gives,
而是它什么时候挡不住
it's when.
它一定会发生的
It's gonna happen.
这就是为什么我们要尽快动手
That's why we have to do this soon.
这真是… 我简直无法形容
This is… I don't even have another word for it.
太可怕了
This is terrifying.
整个都太吓人了
All of it.
但是听起来也似乎没有其他办法
But it doesn't sound like there's any other way.
也许有
Maybe there is.
我是说 我们就不能加固一下薄弱的地方吗
I mean, couldn't we just build up the weak spots?
我可以画个草图
I could draw up plans.
我当年和雷格一起建了围墙
I worked on the wall with reg.
还有施工队在…
Construction crew…
我们可以尝试修复那个漏洞
we can try and make it safe.
就算我们加固了 那些行尸的声音
Even if we could, the sound of those walkers.
也在不停地吸引更多行尸
is drawing more and more every day.
加固那个出口没有什么用
Building up the exits won't change that.
我们按瑞克说的做
We're gonna do what Rick says,
照他的计划来
the plan he's laid out.
我跟大家说过 达里尔会把它们引开
I told you all, we're gonna have Daryl leading them away.
我也去
Me, too.
我开车和他一起
I'll take a car, ride next to him.
不能让他一个人去
Can't just be him.
我来引着它们移动 达里尔确保它们跟紧了
I'll keep 'em coming, Daryl keeps 'em from getting sloppy.
我和她一起去
I'll go with her.
一个人撑全程太辛苦了
It's a long way to white-knuckle it solo.
我们分两个小组
We'll have two teams.
在森林的两边协助计划进行
One on each side of the forest helping manage this thing.
我们从现在开始就需要有人设岗值班
We're gonna have a few people on watch from now on.
就让罗西塔 斯潘塞 还有霍利来做
Rosita, Spencer, and Holly.
他们除外
So they're out.
还有谁参加
So who's in?
我
Me.
你应该盯着她点
You should keep an eye on her.
继续按你说的计划做
Keep going with the plans you talked about.
我知道 但这很重要
I know, but this is important.
她也很重要
She's important.
现在人人自危
People are scared.
他们需要看到她平安归来
They need to see her come back.
这不是唯一原因
That's not the only reason.
是 并不止这个原因
Yeah, it isn't.
好吧
Okay.
我加入
I'm in.
我也想帮忙
I'd like to help as well.
不行 还有谁
No. Who else?
我们需要更多人手
We need more.
我们不能这么干
There's got to be another play.
我们不可能控制得了那么多
We can't just control that many.
我之前说过 赶行尸就像放牧一样
I said it before, walkers herd up.
如果有东西吸引它们它们就会沿着一个方向走
They'll follow a path if something's drawing them.
这就是为什么我们能把它们一网打尽
That's how we can get 'em all at once.
然后呢 我们就应该相信你吗
So, what? We're supposed to just take your word for it?
我们就应该乖乖跟从你 即使你之前…
We're all supposed to just fall in line behind you after…
之前什么
After what?
之前你到处喊打喊杀
After you wave a gun around.
乱嚷乱叫 用枪威胁别人
screaming, pointing it at people.
还打死了一个人
After you shoot a man in the face.
- 之前你… - 够了
- After you… - Enough!
我去
I'll do it.
我也去
Me, too.
无论你需要怎样 我加入
Whatever you need, I'm in.
还有人参加吗
Now who else?
我加入
I'll go.
我们必须这样做 我需要出份力
We have to do this. I need to help.
你确定你能行
You sure you can handle it?
你需要人手
You need people.
我们会成功的 我们会保护这个地方
We'll make this work. We'll keep this place safe.
保护我们的家 我们能做到的
Keep our families safe. We will.
把你计划再说一遍
The plan. Go through it again.
伙计 他刚才说过了
Man, he just said it.
详细地再讲一遍
Every part again.
包括具体的细节
The exact plan.
马歇尔大道与雷丁大道交叉路口
Marshall and Redding.
- 我们在这儿把它们向西引 - 怎么引
- We force them west here. - How?
我们把其他路封住
We block it off.
所以他们只能沿一个方向走
so they can only go one way,
向西 远离社区
west, away from the community.
用什么把路封住
Block it off with what?
汽车
Cars.
用那些旅行车 大卡车
We'll use the rvs, some of the bigger trucks,
首尾相连地停住
park them end to end.
我们会把它们引开
We'll be drawing them away.
他们会一直往外走
They're gonna keep moving.
是 但是引开那么多
Yeah, but that many?
就用区区几辆小车
Just bouncing off some sedans?
然后当它们从这儿通过之后
And then when they start slipping through.
那些掉队的会分散其他的注意力
and the ones that walk away start distracting the rest.
而你们的计划就失败了
and you stop drawing them away?
他说得有道理
Man's got a point.
我们有一些板子
We got plates.
工地上那种很大的金属板
The big-ass metal ones from the construction site.
我们可以用它们来加固通道
We can use them to fortify the whip wall.
这样可以帮助分散行尸冲撞的力量
It'd help disperse the force of impact.
让行尸顺畅地被引走
and direct the walkers clean.
就像台球 击打八号球
Like a pool table.
其他的球都会被弹到球袋里
Eight ball, corner pocket.
外面可是一整个行尸军团
That's an army out there.
如果这东西没撑住又会怎么样
And what happens when this doesn't hold?
他们会冲过来 山坡里的这个拐弯
And they push on through. The curve in this hillside.
会让它们掉头向东
is gonna send them right back east.
直直地冲向我们
Right back here.
你们真的要冒这个险吗
You seriously want to risk that?
不
No.
所以你需要帮助我们让它撑住
So you need to help us to make it hold.
你修建了那些墙
These walls, you built them.
所以你已经完成过这样不可能的任务了
So you've already done the impossible.
卡特
Carter.
拜托了
Please.
（马歇尔大道与雷丁大道交叉路口）
喂 你之前说的 我们要顾好自己
Hey, what you said before about us needing to take care of ourselves?
出去找到更多的人
Going out finding more people,
这才是顾好我们自己
that is taking care of ourselves.
当然 决定权在你
Your call, though.
谢谢
Thanks.
我可以和你们一起去
You know, I can come with all of you.
你和达里尔已经教会了我开枪
You and Daryl have been teaching me how to shoot.
我觉着你已经掌握诀窍了
I think you got the hang of it.
你应该留在后方
You should stay back,
感受其他人的想法
get a feel for how people feel now.
我们和他们还有相处很久
We still got a long way to go with them.
我们会成功的
We'll get there.
表面上 她是在掌权
She's in charge.
但其实掌权的是你
But you're in charge now.
- 这可不是个好办法 - 这是唯一的办法
- This is a bad idea. - This is the only idea.
我觉着里面大概有十多只左右
I think there's something like a dozen in there.
我们退后 往反方向跑 把往两个方向引
We stay back, we get on opposite ends, we draw them to each of us.
- 然后一人杀四个 - 不
- Try and take down four each? - No.
只是我和希恩
This is just me and Heath.
你回去留在后方
You get back and you stay back.
事情要是进展的不顺
Things go south,
你就告诉瑞克 你把它们引走了
you tell Rick and you draw them away.
往后退
Just move back.
他害死了诺亚
He got Noah killed?
是的
He did.
他所做的还不止这样
He did more than that.
他把格伦骗进树林试图杀掉他
He lured Glenn into the woods and tried to kill him.
什么
What the hell?
- 没错 - 什么
- Yeah. - What?
格伦说我大可以告诉所有人
Glenn told me I could tell everyone if that's what I wanted to do.
之前尼古拉斯差点被赶出去
Could get Nicholas exiled.
被赶到外面自生自灭
He'd die out there.
本可以那样做
Could have done that.
你现在也可以这样做
You could do that now.
他害死了诺亚还试图杀死格伦
He got Noah killed and he tried to kill Glenn?
格伦救了大家
Glenn saves people.
即使大家都能接受
Even people like that.
但我怎么样都接受不了
I couldn't accept it either.
但我想到了之前的你
But then I thought about you.
想起了我人生中最幽暗的日子
How we were on different sides of that fence.
我们站在监狱栅栏的两侧
on the worst day of my life.
但你现在却是世上我最在乎的人之一
And now you're one of the most important people in the world to me.
一切都会好起来的
Things can get better.
我们能让一切好起来
We can make them better.
现在告诉我你想怎么做
You tell me what you want to do.
我全听你的 好吗？
I'm just gonna follow your lead, okay?
好
Okay.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
准备好了吗？
You ready?
没 不过看你是不会等我们准备好了…
No. But since you're doing this thing anyway…
开始了
All right.
他们靠近了
They're still coming.
交给你了
Get it.
好样的
Good.
走吧
Let's go.
喝吧
Here you go.
多谢
Oh, thank you.
你是卡罗尔 对吗？
It's Carol, right?
对
Yeah.
你跟着瑞克多久了？
You been with Rick long?
从亚特兰大开始
Since Atlanta.
你也是警察吗？
And were you a cop, too?
怎么这么说？
Why would you think that?
你一直在观察
You're always watching.
你看起来…
You always…
时刻准备着
Seem ready.
准备什么
For what?
就是 解决问题
You know, to handle things.
很会说话嘛
Aren't you sweet?
怎么了
What is it?
一些「调皮的」行尸离开大部队了
Got some looky-loos taking a little constitutional off the shoulder.
他们开始散开走了
They starting a damn walkout.
要让达里尔把他们引回来吗
You want to have Daryl circle back?
不用
No.
继续开车 我很快就回来
Keep moving. I'll catch up.
艾伯拉罕
Abraham.
傻大个
Idiot.
来啊
Come on!
我的车就在那儿 混蛋
This is my ride, asshole.
嘿 瞧瞧我
Well, look at me.
你没看到那天晚上
You didn't see Reg.
雷格被杀得情形
the night he got it.
那可真惨
That was a mess.
还有皮特
And Pete.
他的脸就…
His face just…
像火山口那样炸开了
Blowing up like Pompeii.
就在我们所有人眼前
right when we were cheek to cheek.
我总觉得耳朵里还有他的脑浆
I still think I got some of his brains in my ear.
瞧瞧后面的大军
Well, look at that.
不错
All right.
事情又回到我们所计划的那样了
Everything is aces again.
你刚那是在干什么？
What the hell are you doing?
我只是让那帮蠢行尸别掉队
I'm just grabbing the bull by the nutsack.
我在生存 亲爱的
I'm living, darling,
就跟你一样
just like you.
我还没来得及说
I haven't had a chance to say it yet,
雷格的事 我真的很遗憾
but I'm sorry about reg.
他是个聪明 善良的人
He was smart and kind.
他是个好人
He was a good man.
这个决定很正确 我们需要这样做
It was the right call. We need this.
还有呢？
What else?
说出来
You need to tell me.
在社区内 每个人也该配上武器
People need to be armed inside the walls.
他们需要锻炼
They need to be trained, everyone.
等等
Stop.
他们来了
Here they come.
卡特 注意那边
Carter, heads up.
用铲子打 开枪会引来更多行尸
Use your shovels. The guns will draw more.
帮帮我们
Help us.
你能行的 你们都要学会这样做
You can do this. You need to, all of you.
摩根 别插手
Morgan, don't!
你说过你不想再冒任何险了
You said you don't take chances anymore.
快没时间了
Time is running out.
他说明天要演习
He's talking about a dry run tomorrow. That's it.
瑞克阻止了皮特 他阻止了皮特
Rick stopped Pete. He stopped him.
这和除掉家暴者无关
This is not taking out a wife-beater.
他是杀人凶手 卡特
He was a murderer, Carter.
瑞克的计划就等于去送死
What Rick wants to do is suicide.
我很抱歉 斯潘塞 狄安娜已经神志不清了
I'm sorry, Spencer, but Deanna is asleep at the wheel.
所以这就靠我们了 我们得阻止瑞克
So it's on us. We have got to stop him.
那个牧师说的关于瑞克和那伙人的事
What the priest said about him, about these people,
他说的对
he was right.
在我们动手之前
How many more of us have to die.
还要有多少自己人白白牺牲
before we do something?
再晚就来不及
'Cause pretty soon it's gonna be too late.
卡特 你要十分小心
Carter, you need to be really careful here.
你是说我们去找狄安娜跟她说…
You're talking about us going to Deanna and telling her…
不 我没说要去找谁谈
no, I'm not talking about talking some more.
我说的不是谈话 会议什么的
About meetings. I'm not talking about that.
简单粗暴 在他杀我们之前
Plain and simple, we kill him.
我们去杀了他
before he kills us.
你好
Hello.
卡特
Carter.
- 他都听到了 - 我没有
- He heard. - I didn't.
- 我 我没听到… - 卡特
- I mean, I didn't… - Carter.
他都听到了
He heard.
卡特 别 你不能这样
Carter, don't. You can't.
这是怎么回事？
What the hell is going on?
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
我要从你手中夺回这里
I'm taking this place back from you.
这就是你们在这儿讨论的？
That's what you were talking about in here?
是他一个人这么打算的
That's what he was talking about.
要是我 我会让人把风的
See, I would have… I would have set up some lookouts.
那才是聪明的做法
That would have been the smart thing.
知道吗 要是我…
You know, if I happened to…
你真以为你能从我手中夺回这里吗？
You really think you're gonna take this community from us?
从格伦 米琼恩手中？
From Glenn? From Michonne?
从达里尔手中？从我手中？
From Daryl? From me?
你明白你在跟谁说话吗？
Do you have any idea who you're talking to?
- 是我一个人说的 - 什么？
- It was just me. - What?
都是… 我一个人的主意
It was… it was just me.
杀了我吧
Just… just kill me.
瑞克
Rick.
我没事
I'm good.
好着呢
你可以试着和我们一起
You can try to work with us.
你可以试着活下去
You can try to survive.
你会这么做吗？
Would you do that?
起作用了
It's working.
你是对的
You were right.
各位 是时候结束了
Everyone, we need to finish this.
我们得继续移动 然后将尸群从前往后排好
We have to keep moving and fan out down that thing front to back.
就像维持游行秩序的警察
Like we said, cops at a parade.
格伦 你在后面
Glenn, you take the back.
- 你拿着另一个对讲机 - 好的
- You got the other walkie. - Got it.
要是尸群散了 我们就开枪
If it gets sloppy, we fire our weapons,
把它们引回路上
pull them back on track.
我去前面 好 一个接一个
I'll hit the front. Okay, one after the other.
托宾 它们散开了
Tobin, they're breaking off.
我们该怎么做？
What do you want us to do?
开枪把他们引回路上
Fire your guns and draw them back.
屋外很舒服
It's nice out.
是啊
Yeah.
希望你不要介意
Hope you don't mind.
我想晚上吹吹风
I wanted to enjoy the evening a little.
我那屋没有门廊 所以…
and I don't have a porch over there, so…
收拾你的东西
Get your stuff.
你应该和我们一起住在这边
You should stay with us over here.
有多余的屋子？
You got room?
我们会搞定的
We'll make it.
我们不需要再那样做了
We don't need to do that anymore.
摩根 我了解你
I know you, Morgan.
即便这是第一次
Even if this is the first time.
想抱抱她吗？
You want to hold her?
好啊
Okay.
这是摩根
This is Morgan.
他是我的一个朋友
He's a friend of mine.
嗨
Hey.
Hi.
好了
Okay.
让我瞧瞧你
Let me have a look at you.
你是在军械库时和卡特一起的…
You with that man Carter, in the armory…
原来是你
that's you.
你还是和当初我在金县遇见时一样
You're still the same man I met in king county.
你是那个回来 还告诉我事情没结束的人
The one that came back and told me it wasn't over.
是你
That was you.
和现在我面前的这个人 一模一样
Same you that's right in front of me right now.
我想杀了他
I wanted to kill him.
这样就简单多了
So it would be easier.
这样我就不用担心
So I wouldn't have to worry.
因为他那种秉性
about how he could screw up.
他会通多少篓子 做多少蠢事
or what stupid thing he'd do next because that's who he is.
像他这种人现在就不该活着
Just somebody who shouldn't be alive now.
我真想杀了他
I wanted to kill him.
但我突然想到…
But all that hit me and…
我不用非杀他不可了
I realized I didn't have to do it.
他还不明白
He doesn't get it.
像他那样的人…
Somebody like that…
迟早有天会死的
They're gonna die no matter what.
我要死了
Oh, I'm dead.
卡特 呼吸
Carter, take a breath.
卡特
Carter.
安静点
Oh, god! Be quiet. Shh.
卡特 卡特 嘘 嘘
Oh, god. Carter. Carter, shh.
你得安静下来
You got to be quiet.
嘘
Shh.
起效了
It's working.
枪声让那群家伙又回到了路上
The gunfire is bringing them back on the road.
- 你盯着点它们 托宾 - 收到
- You got them, Tobin. - Copy that.
谁在尖叫？
What was that screaming?
是卡特
That was Carter.
他脸上被咬了一口
He got bit right in the face.
我为了不让他尸变
I stopped him.
在把它们引去那片树林前
We have a good hour.
我们还有整整一个小时
until we have 'em to green.
然后我们把它们交给达里尔 萨莎 艾伯拉罕
when we hand them off to Daryl, Sasha, and Abraham.
你回去给大家说说到底发生了什么
Why don't you head back, tell everyone what's happening?
他们应该知道
They should know.
是 瑞克 我只是…
Okay, Rick, I just…
你能做到吗？
will you do that for me?
那个我来解决
I'll take care of that one.
米琼恩 你来选点
Michonne, you take point.
我知道那是什么感觉
I know it's how it is.
我知道
I do.
是啊
Yeah.
我也知道
I do, too.
嘿
Hey.
我想为明天多准备些照明弹
I was just getting more flares for tomorrow.
我知道我没有…
I know I haven't…
我只是… 我想如果让事情顺其自然的话
I just… I just thought it might be best.
说不定才是最好的
if I let things be for a while.
罗恩告诉我发生的事了
Ron told me what happened.
我想和你谈谈那事
Yeah, I wanted to talk to you about that.
他不应该出现在那里
He shouldn't have been out there.
是的 他不应该
No, he shouldn't have.
你说得对
You're right.
但你不能那样对他说话 瑞克
But you can't talk to him like that, Rick.
你不能碰他
You can't touch him.
你不能
Not you.
罗恩必须仔细听我讲的每一句话
Ron needed to hear every word I said.
这才是我抓他的原因 我不是在生气
That's why I grabbed him. I wasn't angry.
我只是在告诉他真相
I was just telling him the truth.
如果真相来源于你 他听不进去的
If it's coming from you, he can't hear it.
你得明白这一点
You got to understand that.
他需要知道怎么保护他自己
He needs to know how to handle himself.
- 我可以教他 我可以教你 - 瑞克
- I can teach him. I can teach you. - Rick.
- 你得知道怎么做 - 瑞克
- You need to know how. - Rick.
当我知道我们可以有枪时
When I found out we could have them,
我开始让罗西塔教我怎么射击
I asked Rosita to start showing me how.
好吗？她教我 然后我再教罗恩
Okay? She's gonna teach me and I'm gonna teach Ron.
再教山姆
and I'm gonna teach Sam.
我听见了你在会上对我们说的那些
Look I heard what you were saying to us at the meeting.
还有以前在我家 你知道
And at my house before, you know.
我会战斗的 瑞克
I am gonna fight, Rick.
好了 这是终点线
All right, this is the finish line.
我们把它们引到这 我们就撤退
When we make it to green, we fall back.
这些沟渠土坎会把它们困在大路上
The ditches and ridges will keep them on the road.
我们回家 但 达里尔 萨莎 艾伯拉罕
We head home, but Daryl, Sasha, and Abraham.
会再把它们引到二十英里以外
take them the rest of the way, 20 miles more.
好了 我们出发
All right, let's go.
问你个问题
Got a question for you.
就明天公路之旅前的一个小疑问
Just some intel before our little road trip tomorrow.
问吧
Ask me.
你这么做 是因为你想寻死吗？
You doing this 'cause you want to die?
不是
No.
我们将引它们通过这里
We're gonna take 'em right past here.
那些声音会吸引它们
All that noise could distract them.
今晚回去的时候把这清理干净
We'll clear it on our way back tonight.
我们不想明天出任何意外
We don't want any surprises tomorrow.
你要为你的行为
Hey, what you've done,
承担后果
you're gonna sit with it a while,
因为我不想你明天出去
'cause I don't want you out here tomorrow.
你还没准备好
You're not ready.
你会的
You will be.
就快了 我向你保证
Some time soon, I'll make sure of it.
然后你就好好做
And then you start to make it right.
谢谢
Thank you.
这听起来确实不实际
I know this sounds insane,
但这本来就是一个疯狂的世界
but this is an insane world.
在他们过来之前 我们要主动出击
We have to come for them before they come for us.
就这么简单
It's that simple.
该死的发生什么事了？
What the hell is happening?
是号角声还是什么
It's a horn or something.
后面队伍的僵尸开始离队了
It's pulling the back half off the road.
天呐
Oh, god.
不管那是什么 很远
Whatever that is, it's far.
它听起来 像是从… 家那边传来的
It sounds like it's coming from… home.